<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>devlog on Sledgehog Software</title>
    <link>https://sledgehogsoftware.com/blog/tags/devlog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in devlog on Sledgehog Software</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2020 Sledgehog Software</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sledgehogsoftware.com/blog/tags/devlog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cubytes Devlog #003 - Hiatus No More</title>
      <link>https://sledgehogsoftware.com/blog/posts/2019-03-30-cubytes-devlog-003-hiatus-no-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sledgehogsoftware.com/blog/posts/2019-03-30-cubytes-devlog-003-hiatus-no-more/</guid>
      <description>After quite a while with radio silence (nearly two months&amp;hellip;) coming from Sledgehog Software, here comes this devlog. Hooray.
First of all, it was a fat break. Apparently, my mind thought it was too long after Godot 3.1 was announced so I started work on it recently. Here&amp;rsquo;s things I&amp;rsquo;ve changed, added, or deleted.
Balancing As more and more levels were added to Cubytes, a form of design debt came up with the older levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Development, Head First</title>
      <link>https://sledgehogsoftware.com/blog/posts/2019-01-15-web-development-head-first/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sledgehogsoftware.com/blog/posts/2019-01-15-web-development-head-first/</guid>
      <description>When I first thought of the prospect of making my own company, I quickly realized that I needed to have some sort of online presence (read: website).
This idea was a little bit scary for me. I had no idea how to make a website, let alone host one. So, I&amp;rsquo;m going to tell you how I did it, and also show you some problems I faced.
Step 1: Skipping most people&amp;rsquo;s Step 1 Okay, here&amp;rsquo;s the deal: I pretty much knew the basics of HTML and CSS, meaning I understood a lot more than other people starting out with Web Development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cubytes Devlog #002</title>
      <link>https://sledgehogsoftware.com/blog/posts/2019-01-01-cubytes-devlog-002/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sledgehogsoftware.com/blog/posts/2019-01-01-cubytes-devlog-002/</guid>
      <description>As 2018 left and 2019 came, Cubytes received some tweaks and thoughts to the core game added to it recently.
The Story of Cubytes Looking back on the previously released Alphas, there really wasn&amp;rsquo;t any sense of story. The closest thing that came to a story was the Block Tutorial popups&amp;hellip; which are really just textbox tutorials that have no kind of overarching narrative.
To make it clear, there is a planned Story (though I&amp;rsquo;m a little murky on an ending) with a planned narrator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cubytes Devlog #001</title>
      <link>https://sledgehogsoftware.com/blog/posts/2018-12-29-cubytes-devlog-001/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sledgehogsoftware.com/blog/posts/2018-12-29-cubytes-devlog-001/</guid>
      <description>Why a Devlog? While it is indeed quite late into development, which might not make sense, however it&amp;rsquo;s something to show my day to day progress. This is more important now than it was earlier on, as I&amp;rsquo;m planning on releasing the game in Q1/Q2 2018 and Cubytes is in closed development. Read the last post for more information on that.
Regardless, what have I done since the release of Alpha 7?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>