<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>website on Sledgehog Software</title>
    <link>https://sledgehogsoftware.com/blog/tags/website/</link>
    <description>Recent content in website on Sledgehog Software</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2020 Sledgehog Software</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sledgehogsoftware.com/blog/tags/website/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Alive; Or, how I came to revamp this blog.</title>
      <link>https://sledgehogsoftware.com/blog/posts/2020-02-23-its-alive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sledgehogsoftware.com/blog/posts/2020-02-23-its-alive/</guid>
      <description>The blog is alive! And much different!
&amp;hellip; Wait, how long was I gone for? 11 MONTHS? And what the ever living fuck is &amp;lsquo;A Frail Qubit&amp;rsquo;?
God, where to begin?
A Sorefully Needed Update As some of you either have no idea who I am (statistically, that&amp;rsquo;s a minority&amp;hellip;), I&amp;rsquo;d like to explain who I am and (to those of you who has been needing at least an explanation) what the fuck I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Development, Head First</title>
      <link>https://sledgehogsoftware.com/blog/posts/2019-01-15-web-development-head-first/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sledgehogsoftware.com/blog/posts/2019-01-15-web-development-head-first/</guid>
      <description>When I first thought of the prospect of making my own company, I quickly realized that I needed to have some sort of online presence (read: website).
This idea was a little bit scary for me. I had no idea how to make a website, let alone host one. So, I&amp;rsquo;m going to tell you how I did it, and also show you some problems I faced.
Step 1: Skipping most people&amp;rsquo;s Step 1 Okay, here&amp;rsquo;s the deal: I pretty much knew the basics of HTML and CSS, meaning I understood a lot more than other people starting out with Web Development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>URL and Closed Development</title>
      <link>https://sledgehogsoftware.com/blog/posts/2018-12-28-url-and-closed-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sledgehogsoftware.com/blog/posts/2018-12-28-url-and-closed-development/</guid>
      <description>The blog now has a custom URL! This took some time to sort out (Mostly DNS related issues&amp;hellip; this Blogger instance is running on a DreamHost DNS, which is the main website is setup. Figuring that out was a little hard.) but finally I think it&amp;rsquo;s fine and the two websites should stay up.
I have moved development to a private Azure git instance, just so my commercial game isn&amp;rsquo;t on github to build and deploy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>