<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>release on Sledgehog Software</title>
    <link>https://sledgehogsoftware.com/blog/tags/release/</link>
    <description>Recent content in release on Sledgehog Software</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2020 Sledgehog Software</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sledgehogsoftware.com/blog/tags/release/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Alive; Or, how I came to revamp this blog.</title>
      <link>https://sledgehogsoftware.com/blog/posts/2020-02-23-its-alive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sledgehogsoftware.com/blog/posts/2020-02-23-its-alive/</guid>
      <description>The blog is alive! And much different!
&amp;hellip; Wait, how long was I gone for? 11 MONTHS? And what the ever living fuck is &amp;lsquo;A Frail Qubit&amp;rsquo;?
God, where to begin?
A Sorefully Needed Update As some of you either have no idea who I am (statistically, that&amp;rsquo;s a minority&amp;hellip;), I&amp;rsquo;d like to explain who I am and (to those of you who has been needing at least an explanation) what the fuck I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alpha 7</title>
      <link>https://sledgehogsoftware.com/blog/posts/2018-12-24-alpha-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sledgehogsoftware.com/blog/posts/2018-12-24-alpha-7/</guid>
      <description>The wait for Alpha 7 is finally over, and with it comes brand-new additions such as Lasers, Cheat Codes, and Revamped Graphics!
Links  Windows (64-bit) Windows (32-bit) macOS (FAT) Linux-X11  Changelog  Added a floor to all Arcade and Story Levels. Added Saving of Story Mode progress (Does not currently save progress within alevel, just what level you&amp;rsquo;re on and some statistics). Added Highscores for Arcade Mode Levels. Added a Timed Laser and Laser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alpha 6</title>
      <link>https://sledgehogsoftware.com/blog/posts/2018-09-12-alpha-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sledgehogsoftware.com/blog/posts/2018-09-12-alpha-6/</guid>
      <description>Alpha 6 is now available to download!
The main new features for this release is Arcade Mode and Black Holes!
Links  Windows (64-bit) Windows (32-bit) Linux  Changelog  Added Arcade Mode. Added a completed game flag. Added (but not implemented) Cheat Codes. Added a black hole SFX. Added black holes. Added an additional background effect. Added Explosion and Endblock particle effects. Added Levels 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>